https://camptrillium.com/privacy/

Camp Ooch & Camp Trillium
About UsOur StoryFinancial InformationOur PartnershipsBoard of DirectorsBlog UpdatesCampersOverviewProgramsDatesComing to CampCamp SitesOuR IslandRainbow LakeStaff/VolunteersStaffVolunteeringNursingSupportersFundraisingEventsRentals DonateContact Our ProgramsVolunteeringMake a DonationFundraise for us
We recognize your right to confidentiality and pledge to protect your privacy. We are members of and adhere to the privacy guidelines of both the Canadian Marketing Association and the Canadian Centre of Philanthropy.
Here’s how we keep our pledge:
Overall
We only collect personally identifying information (for example, user name, donor name, e-mail address, mailing address, employer, and telephone number, etc.) about registered users, donors or other Site users (collectively, the “Users”) when knowingly provided by them.
Registration
Personally identifiable information of Users will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the User’s prior consent. However, we may use registration or other information in the following ways:
To guide development of new features and services relevant to Site UsersTo provide advertisers with summary – never individual – information about our Site’s overall usage patterns; andTo focus advertising based on your preferences.
Camp Trillium will be pleased to inform you of the existence, any use, and disclosure of personally identifying information, and provide you with access to that Personal Information, within 30 (thirty) days of a receipt of a written request directed to Camp Trillium, 940 Queensdale Avenue East, Hamilton, Ontario L8V 1N4, subject to exceptions assigned by law.
If you wish to have your email address deleted from our database, email us at reception@camptrillium.com and include the EXACT words “CANCEL MAIL” in the body of your email. Please allow two to three business days for the actual cancellation to take effect.
Security
Camp Trillium uses Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) encryption technology to ensure the integrity and privacy of the personal and credit card information you pass to us via the Internet when you make an online donation or place an order online. However, to take advantage of this, you must use a compatible browser.
Use of Cookies
What is a cookie? Generally, cookies are small text files a website can use to recognize repeat users and ease the ongoing access to and use of the website. They do not come onto a user’s system nor do they pose a threat to a user’s files. Users should be aware that Camp Trillium cannot control the use of cookies by advertisers or third parties hosting data for Camp Trillium. Except as described herein, this Site does not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with any third parties. However, if a User does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature. Please note that cookies may be necessary to provide the User with certain features (for example, customized delivery of information) available on Camp Trillium’s site.
Opt-Out Options
We give Users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:
Opting not to provide certain personal information when registering.Opting not to participate in Interactive Areas.Opting not to receive email from Camp Trillium.
You do not need to give personal information to receive information from this site.
User Submissions
Camp Trillium appreciates your feedback!
Any information such as remarks, suggestions, questions, correspondence, comments, creative ideas, graphics, or other information communicated to Camp Trillium through this Site, (collectively, called the “Submission”) shall be treated as non-confidential. You agree that you will not upload or transmit any Submission that infringes any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary rights of any party.
Your Submission becomes the property of Camp Trillium and the Camp Trillium shall be free to use the Submission on an unrestricted basis for any purpose whatsoever.
Use of Interactive Areas
If you use the Site’s donation “pledge” forms, employment surveys, questionnaires, contests, profiles and any other interactive areas (collectively referred to as “Interactive Areas”), you are solely responsible for your own communications and the consequences of submitting those communications. Camp Trillium does not assume any responsibility for the consequences of any Interactive Area communications on or arising from use of the Camp Trillium Site.
Content Use License
Upon acceptance of these Terms and Conditions, permission is granted for you to temporarily view, copy, print or download a single copy of the materials on this Site solely for your personal, non-commercial use.
The contents of the Site include but are not limited to text, graphics, images, logos, buttons, proprietary software icons, compilations (meaning the collection, arrangement and assembly), reading lists, libraries, updates, news, glossary, reviews, health tips, opinions, and other material including any modifications thereto (“Content”), are protected by copyright laws. Camp Trillium will constantly be making changes to the Content contained on this Site in light of new information to serve you better.
You may reproduce limited excerpts of the data for personal use only, provided that each such copy contains a copyright notice as follows: © 2008 Camp Trillium. All rights reserved. You may not alter the information in this site in any way without prior written consent of Camp Trillium.
Content is subject to change without notice at the sole editorial discretion of Camp Trillium. If you violate any of these Terms and Conditions, your permission to use the Content automatically terminates and you must immediately destroy any copies you have made of any portion of the Content.
Any questions or concerns can be addressed to Camp Trillium, 940 Queensdale Avenue East, Hamilton, Ontario
Refund Policy
In the event of a discrepancy or error with your online transaction, please contact reception@camptrillium.com . Please include your name, telephone number and the date and amount of your transaction. Camp Trillium is committed to ensuring all discrepancies are resolved within 10 business days.
Share this:FacebookTwitterMorePinterestRedditLinkedInTumblr
Contact Us
Contact Us
Phone: (905) 527-1992
Toll-free: 1-888-999-2267
Fax: 1 (905) 527-5314
Email: reception@camptrillium.com
Mailing Address:
Copyright © 2020 Trillium Childhood Cancer Support Centre · Privacy Policy · Terms of Use
